brandfactoryonline.com 2019-07-08

# BrandFactory

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Company and its subsidiaries, partners, agents and affiliates collect, use, maintain and disclose information collected from users of the Company, website i.e. https:// [www.brandfactoryonline.com](http://www.brandfactoryonline.com/). 

Personal identification information: We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our website, fill out a personal details , and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our website. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number.

Non-personal identification information: We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our website. Non-personal identification information may include the User name, the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information, if any.

Website cookies: Our website may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's website places cookies on their Files for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their website to refuse cookies, or to alert the Users when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the website may not function properly.

How we use collected information: Company may collect and use User's personal information for the following purposes:

To improve customer service:

  * Information provided by Users helps us respond to the customer service requests and support needs, more efficiently.

  * To personalize User experience:

  * We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our website.

  * To improve our website:

  * We may use feedback provided by the User/s to improve our products and services.

  * To run a promotion, contest, survey or other feature.

  * To send the User/s information they agreed to receive about topics of interest to them.

  * To send periodic emails.

  * We may use the email address to respond to the inquiries, questions, and/or other requests of User/s. If User/s decide/s to opt to be part of our mailing list, then the User/s will receive emails about company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User/s would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, they may do so by contacting us via our website.

How we protect User's information: We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of User's personal information and data stored on our website. Sensitive and private data exchange between the website and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

Sharing personal information of User/s: We do not sell, trade, or rent User's personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding User/s with our subsidiaries, our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above

Changes to this privacy policy: Company shall update this privacy policy at its sole discretion. Users are advised to check this page for any changes in the privacy policy and to stay informed about how the personal information of the Users is protected by us. The User/s hereby acknowledge/s and agree/s that it is their responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Your acceptance of these terms: By using this website, the Users signify their acceptance of this policy as may be modified from time to time. The Users are advised not to access this website if they do not agree to our privacy policy. The above mentioned privacy policy shall be applicable for the information and data collected by our call centers as well.

Contacting us: If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this website, or your dealings with this website, please contact us at: Future Lifestyle Fashions Ltd. Brand Factory, Umang Tower, 2 nd Floor, Mind Space, Opp Link Road, Malad (West) Mumbai 400064

**Shipping Policy**

\- We are committed to delivering your order accurately, in good condition, and always on time.

\- Please note all items will be shipped with an invoice mentioning the price, as per Indian Tax Regulations.

1\. What are the delivery charges for pre-paid orders?

For all prepaid purchases over Rs. 999, we will deliver the order to your doorstep for FREE! Delivery charges of Rs. 99 will be applicable on all orders of Rs. 999 or less. We charge the same shipping charges across India.

2\. When will my order be delivered?

Most of our orders are delivered in upto 7 days from date of order. We ship on all working days, except during unforeseen circumstances.

Any order may or may not be confirmed on call for delivery attempt, depending on the courier partner.

3\. How do I track my order?

You will be provided with a docket number for your order with which you can track it on the site of the courier service provider.

In the unlikely event we are unable to deliver any items in your order, be assured, that you will not be charged for that item, or you shall be refunded the full amount charged for the item.

4\. Do you deliver outside India?

Currently we do not deliver to locations outside India.

5\. What can I do if I receive a damaged product?

If you believe that the product is not in good condition, or if the packaging is tampered with or damaged, before accepting delivery of the goods, please refuse to take delivery of the package, and mail us at care@brandfactoryonline.com, or call our Customer Care at 18002679900 mentioning your Order Number. We shall make our best efforts to ensure that a replacement delivery is made to you at the earliest or refund the amount.

6\. What happens if I wish to cancel an order?

You can cancel the order which has not been shipped. In this case we will refund the full order amount including the delivery charges.

7\. What if brandfactoyonline.com cancels my order?

In the event we have to cancel any items in your order, if you have paid using a credit card/debit card/net banking, your bank shall be instructed to refund the amount within 7 working days. However, the actual credit to your account will depend on your banks processing time. If you do not receive a credit within this time, please check with your bank and let us know if you face any issues with the same.

8\. What if I opt for partial return after using coupon?

If return is opted for an item in an invoice on which coupon was availed, the amount of the coupon will not be adjusted, and neither will the coupon be reusable. This rule applies on partial return as well against such invoices.

**Newsletters  **  
If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. You may unsubscribe from these communications at any time by following the instruction contained within each of the communications you receive.

**Service-related Announcements**

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.

**Facebook Connect**

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

**Tell-A-Friend**  
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site or to share your wish list, we will ask you for your friend's name and/or email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site or view your wish list. Brandfactoryonline.com stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at care@brandfactoryonline.com to request that we remove this information from our database.

**Service Providers**

We use other third parties such as a shipping company to fulfill orders, and a payment gateway company to bill you for goods and services, and an email service provider to send out emails on our behalf. We use Live Chat to assist you if you have questions while using our site or regarding your order. When you sign up for our services, we will share your personal information as necessary for the third party to provide that service.

**Legal Disclaimer**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Website.

**Business Transitions**

In the event the Company or brandfactoryonline.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of Brand Factory or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. 

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at care@brandfactoryonline.com. We will respond to your request to access within 24 hours. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Security  
** The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. We use persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's 'help' file. We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don't have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited The use of cookies by our [partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers] is not covered by our privacy statement. We do have access or control over these cookies. Our [partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers] use session ID cookies [to make it easier for you to navigate our site, in order for you to use the shopping cart, etc.

**Log Files**

As is true of most Web sites, we use third-party tracking services to gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

**Links to Other Sites**

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by the company or brandfactoryonline.com . Please be aware that we, , are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site. Changes in this Privacy Statement We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent and we only use your information as described in the Privacy Policy. We view protection of your privacy as a very important community principle. We understand clearly that you and Your Information is one of our most important assets. We store and process Your Information on computers located in the India that are protected by physical as well as technological security devices. We use third parties to verify and certify our privacy principles. If you object to your Information being transferred or used in this way please do not use the Site.
